sure you can imagine that with six
相信你能想象有六个
children we had discipline issues yes
孩子我们有纪律问题是的
lots of memories of discipline issues
很多关于纪律问题的记忆
how many of you saw the video or heard
你们有多少人看过这个视频或听过
about the judge beating his daughter a
关于法官殴打他的女儿
few weeks ago
几个星期前
how many watched the video I watched it
有多少人看过我看过的视频
and that was not what you're gonna hear
那不是你会听到的
right now in the next 50 minutes or 45
现在在接下来的50分钟或45分钟
minutes
分钟
that was clearly child abuse and
这显然是虐待儿童和
obviously angry swearing parent taking
显然愤怒的咒骂父母服用
out wrath on a 16 year old I can see why
对一个16岁的孩子发怒，我明白为什么
that video would be controversial but it
那段视频会有争议但是它
sure has stirred up in our culture again
肯定再次激起了我们的文化
the whole issue of spanking etc this
打屁股等这整个问题
week I was asked the question about
上周有人问我这样一个问题
parents who have adopted foster children
谁已经采用寄养儿童 父母
and the LA County social child
和洛杉矶县的社交孩子
protective services are giving them
保护性服务正在给予他们
issues with their adopted children
他们收养孩子的问题
because one of their teenage sons who
因为他们中的一个十几岁的儿子
was first a foster child turn them in
是第一个养育孩子的人
for spanking lots of issues related to
打击很多与之相关的问题
this topic that we have for our last
这是我们最后一个话题
hour by the way I think you guys need to
顺便说一下我认为你们需要的时间
give yourselves a hand
给自己一个手
for 30 hours of sitting here so
坐在这里 30个小时
celebrate
庆祝
I'm sure you've experienced this either
我相信你也经历过这种情况
in public experiencing the spoiled child
在公共场合体验被宠坏的孩子
just out-of-control child throwing a
刚刚失控的孩子扔了一个
temper tantrum and you were wishing to
脾气暴躁， 你想要
yourself I wish that parent knew how to
亲爱的， 我希望父母知道如何做
discipline that child I read this shirt
那个孩子我读这件衬衫的纪律
one time one on this little girl the
一次一个关于这个小女孩的
shirt said this little girl just little
衬衫说这个小女孩只是一点点
girl big bold letters on the shirt it's
女孩在衬衫上大胆的字母
all about me just deal with it I thought
关于我的一切只是处理它，我想
wow that's bold
哇，这很大胆
so we've either experienced the spoiled
所以我们要么经历过被宠坏了
child that's out of control or we've
我们失控的孩子
experienced the angry parent irrational
经历了愤怒的父母非理性
parent screaming in Walmart or the
父母在沃尔玛或其中尖叫
grocery store and we've wished the same
杂货店，我们也希望如此
thing I wish that parent really knew how
我希望父母真的知道如何
to discipline a child so the last hour
在最后一小时训练孩子
here is about discipline parental
这是关于纪律的父母
discipline one of the interesting things
训练一件有趣的事情
in your notes is something I just got
在你的笔记中我只是得到了
about two weeks ago because of the
大约两个星期前， 因为
issues that are coming up with spanking
将出现的体罚问题
and it's the Attorney General's opinion
这是司法部长的意见
from the state of California on
来自 加利福尼亚州的上 州
California's spanking law now we could
现在我们可以加利福尼亚州的打屁股法
be here for hours
在这里待了几个小时
talking about this topic of parental
谈论父母的这个话题
discipline and disciplining children so
纪律和纪律的孩子
I obviously cannot go through this
我显然无法通过这个
document in detail and I am NOT a lawyer
详细记录，我不是律师
even though I did ask a lawyer this past
尽管我过去曾经问过一位律师
week who is a biblical counselor and
一周谁是圣经辅导员和
he's also a lawyer I asked him his
他也是律师，我问过他
opinion on what is the current climate
关于当前气候的看法
in California toward the the spanking
在加利福尼亚州的打屁股
law so I have his opinion in your notes
法律所以我在你的笔记中有他的意见
also so let's think about this topic of
我们也要考虑这个话题
discipline you see there right under the
纪律你在那里看到了
introduction my thesis statement for the
介绍我 的论文陈述
time together that Scripture gives clear
在一起的时间是圣经给明确
guidance on the discipline of children
关于儿童纪律的指导
either through direct commands or
通过直接命令或
precepts or through principles that
戒律或原则
shape our thinking in other words what
塑造我们的思维，换句话说是什么
you're hearing is a sufficiency of
你听到的是充足的
Scripture argue
圣经争辩说
again and as Wayne said in his
再次， 正如韦恩在他的说法中所说
introduction this must this might be one
介绍这必须是一个
of the areas where a Christian worldview
基督教世界观的地区
on the discipline of children is
关于儿童的纪律是
directly opposed to what our culture
直接反对我们的文化
says about the discipline of children
关于孩子的纪律说
there is a biblical Christian worldview
有一个圣经的基督教世界观
on the discipline of children now
对孩子的管教，现在
there's some basic ingredients that make
有一些基本的成分， 使
up a a framework or a philosophy for how
如何建立一个框架或哲学
to think about disciplining children so
考虑如此训练孩子
that's my first point general biblical
这是我的第一点一般圣经
principles that just help us think about
只是帮助我们思考的原则
how do we get to this conclusion that
我们如何得到这个 结论，
proverbs talks about the Ephesians 6
谚语谈论以弗所书6
talks about what are some general
谈论什么是一般的
biblical principles the first thing is
圣经原则首先是
Psalm 24 we're not going to turn there
诗篇24我们不会转向那里
the first passage we'll turn to is Titus
我们要转向的第一段是提图斯
3 and I'm going to quote these other
3，我要引用其他这些
ones Psalm 24 verses wanting one and to
那些诗篇24 诗句想要一个和
say the earth is the Lord's and the
说地球是主的和
fullness thereof the world and all it
世界和它的全部丰满
contains that includes our children so
包含我们的孩子
our children really aren't our children
我们的孩子真的不是我们的孩子
they're really from the Lord and they're
他们真的来自主，他们是
given to me as a responsibility to shape
赋予我塑造的责任
for his honor and glory everything is
为了他的荣誉和荣耀，一切都是
the Lord Psalm 24 Psalm 127 1 says
主诗篇24篇诗篇127 1说
children are a heritage from the Lord
孩子是主的遗产
they are a gift from God now that's
他们 现在是上帝的礼物
countercultural
反主流文化
also the the idea that children are a
孩子也是一个想法
blessing and they're a gift from the
祝福，他们是来自的礼物
Lord unfortunately many people don't
不幸的是，许多人没有
think so
这么认为
now Titus chapter 3 and I have to think
现在提图斯第3章和我不得不思考
that part of the reason why they don't
那部分原因是他们没有
think children are blessing is because
认为孩子是祝福是因为
they don't know how to discipline their
他们不知道如何训练自己
children children can be a great
孩子的孩子可以是一个伟大的
blessing if they're being raised in the
祝福，如果他们被提升了
right atmosphere now look at Titus
正确的气氛现在看看提图斯
chapter 3 something radically went wrong
第3章有些根本出错了
at the beginning and Titus 3:3 says this
起初，提多书3：3说这个
that there's something called a sin
有一种叫罪的东西
nature so Titus 3 says but we also once
自然所以提图斯3说，但我们也曾经
were foolish ourselves disobedient
愚蠢自己不听话
deceived enslaved two very
受骗的奴役了两个
it's lusts and pleasures spending our
这是我们的欲望和乐趣
life in malison and be hateful and
生活malison和可恨和
hating one another now the thing that
是彼此相恨现在件事
strikes me about this passage is that
关于这段经文让我印象深刻
this is Paul the former Pharisee writing
这是保罗前法利赛人写的
it and he says we also were foolish
它和他说我们也是愚蠢的
ourselves he recognized even as this one
他们自己也认识到这一点
who had been raised to keep the law
谁被提出来遵守法律
meticulously and his behavior outwardly
一丝不苟地和他的外表行为
would have been meticulous or he would
本来会很细致，或者他会
have tried to have been meticulous with
我曾经尽力一丝不苟
his behavior he knew something was wrong
他的行为他知道有些事情是错的
on the inside and he says we also were
在内部，他说我们也是
foolish disobedient deceived enslaved
愚蠢的不听话欺骗奴役
the various lusts and pleasures spending
各种欲望和快乐消费
our life in malice and envy hateful and
我们生活在恶意和嫉妒中
hating one another so I'm posing a
彼此讨厌，所以我正在构成一个
question in your notes and our culture
你的笔记和我们的文化中的问题
asks this question why do children turn
问这个问题为什么孩子会转
out the way they do is it a nurture
他们做的方式是培养
problem is it a nature problem and I
问题是我和自然问题
don't mean nature as we use the word
我们使用这个词并不意味着自然
nature likes in nature they mean
大自然喜欢自然的意思
genetics it's your biology so is it a
遗传学它是你的生物学，所以它是一个
biology problem is it a nurture problem
生物学问题是一个培育问题
it was your family of origin that's the
这是你的原始家族
terminology that gets used it was your
使用它的术语是你的
family that shaped you to be the way
塑造你成为道路的家庭
that you are or is it a combination of
你是或是它的组合
both or is there another option well do
两者还是有其他选择
genetics shape you of course genetics
遗传学塑造了你当然的遗传学
shape you does your family of origin
塑造你做你的家族血统
shape you of course your family shapes
塑造你当然是你的家庭形状
you but biblically there's something
你，但圣经上有一些东西
deeper going on deeper than genetics
比遗传更深入
deeper than family culture going on and
比家庭文化还要深刻
it's called the sin nature
它被称为罪性
Titus 3:3 Genesis 3 and some verses that
提多书3：3创世纪3和一些经文
we're gonna look at in proverbs make it
我们会用谚语来看待它
very clear that our children are
很清楚，我们的孩子
conceived in sin there is a thing called
在罪中怀有一种叫做的东西
a sin nature so we like to jokingly say
一种罪恶的本性所以我们喜欢开玩笑地说
that babies are and doctor Street
那个婴儿和医生街
probably said this when he was here the
当他在这里的时候可能会说这个
first weekend babies are vipers and
第一个周末的婴儿是毒蛇和
diapers it's a good thing that the Lord
尿布这对主来说是件好事
made him so cute and cuddly
让他如此可爱和可爱
all that selfishness wrapped up in a
所有的自私都包裹在一个
little baby think about what happened in
小宝宝想想发生了什么事
genesis 1 2 & 3 genesis 1 and 2 what was
起源1 2和3的起源1和2是什么
Adam and Eve's basic nature
亚当和夏娃的基本本质
it was outward and upward Genesis 1 & 2
它是向外和向上的创世纪1和2
they were made for each other and they
他们对彼此和他们 作了
were made for relationship with the
是为了与...建立关系
Creator Genesis 3 what happened goes
创造者创世纪3发生了什么事
inward and there's an inward turning
向内，有向内转
toward self and you hear it right at the
走向自我，你听到它的权利在
beginning of chapter 3 when God
第3章开始 时的上帝
confronts Adam and he says this I'm a
面对亚当，他说我是一个
victim the woman you gave me I'm a
受害者你给我的女人我是一个
victim now and that's basically what our
受害者现在，这基本上是我们的
culture says it's your family that
文化说这是你的家人
shaped you to be the way you are or it's
塑造你成为你的方式或它的方式
your genetics it's not you it's your
你的遗传并不是你的遗产
genetics it was your family scripture
遗传学是你的家庭经文
says and here's the principle in your
说，这是你的原则
notes children have a natural bent
注意到孩子们天生弯曲
toward self away from God and away from
走向自我远离神，远离
putting others first I think that's why
把别人放在第一位我觉得这就是原因
the two great Commandments are love God
两条伟大的诫命是爱上帝
and love others and that's what the Holy
并且爱别人，这就是神圣的
Spirit is doing in the gospel is
精神在福音里正在做
changing through progressive
通过进步改变
sanctification changing that natural
成圣改变自然
bent back outward and back upward toward
向后弯曲向外和向上后面朝向
God and toward others and then Matthew
上帝和他人，然后马修
28 again what's our goal these are basic
28又什么是我们的目标这些都是基本的
biblical principles that just kind of
圣经的原则是正中下怀
shape our worldview about why do we
塑造我们为什么做世界观
discipline children Matthew 28 it's
纪律儿童马太福音28章
about making disciples maturity toward
关于让门徒走向成熟
Christ likeness is the goal it's not
基督的形象是不是的目标
just behavior modification to get them
只是行为修改才能得到它们
to behave in the grocery store so I'm
我在杂货店里表现得很好
not embarrassed that's not the goal it's
并不尴尬，这不是它的目标
we're trying to shape them bring them up
我们正试图塑造他们带来他们
Ephesians 6 is work and we're gonna go
以弗所书6章是工作，我们要去
back to that passage bring them up in
回到那个通道养育他们
the nurture and admonition of the Lord
主的培养和训诫
we have a goal beloved that we're headed
我们有一个心爱的目标，我们正在前进
toward it's about maturity mature
走向成熟成熟
citizens mature children who are
公民成熟的孩子谁是
followers of the Lord Jesus Christ it's
主耶稣基督的信徒是
not just outward
不只是向外
conformity so in summary basic biblical
顺从这样总结基本的圣经
principles just kind of shape our
原则只是塑造我们的
thinking to begin with they're from the
他们开始考虑从他们那里开始
Lord so I have a responsibility they've
上帝让我有他们已经责任
been given to me to manage for his honor
被授予我为他的荣誉而管理
and glory but they really belong to him
和荣耀，但他们真的属于他
they have a sin nature because of
他们因罪而具有罪性
Genesis 3 and I'm trying it so they need
创世纪3和我正在尝试它，所以他们需要
direction and what's the direction
方向和方向是什么
Christ likeness they need to know more
基督的形象他们需要了解更多
about their Savior they need to come to
关于他们的救主他们需要来
a relationship with their Savior and
与他们的救主和他们的关系
then grow in their relationship with the
然后与他们的关系成长
Lord now let's go to proverbs and
主现在让我们去谚语和
there's a lot in proverbs about raising
关于抚养的谚语有很多
children I'm not going to go through all
孩子我不打算全部通过
the verses that are in your notes but
你的笔记中的经文但是
I've picked out some of the main
我挑选了一些主要的
passages in Proverbs that talk about
在箴言中谈论的段落
raising children let's go to that first
养育孩子让我们去，首先
one proverbs 13:24 some really clear
一句谚语13:24一些非常清楚
biblical guidance here and we have to
圣经指导在这里，我们必须
ask ourself the question what is a rod
问自己这个问题什么是棒
proverbs 13:24 scripture makes it really
箴言13:24经文使它成真
clear he who spares his rod hates his
清楚他饶了他的杖恨他的
son but he who loves him disciplines him
儿子， 但爱他的人训练他
diligently if there was somebody from
努力， 如果有人来自
secular Child Protective Services here
这里有世俗的儿童保护服务
right now I I was almost thinking I
现在我几乎在想我
could get arrested even for teaching
即使是教学也可能被捕
this that's how countercultural this is
这就是反文化的方式
what is the rod this is considered
什么是杆这被考虑
primitive and would be considered child
原始的，将被视为孩子
abuse to even read a verse like this but
滥用甚至读这样的诗句但是
scripture makes it very clear that if we
经文清楚地表明，如果我们
do not do what this verse says and what
不要做这节经文所说的和什么
other verses are saying that we hate our
其他经文说我们讨厌我们的
children you know why because the
孩子你知道为什么因为
assumption of this verse is that
这节经文的假设就是这样
children have a sin nature part of the
孩子们有罪性的一部分
reason why disciplining like this sounds
为什么像这样训练的原因听起来
so countercultural is because our
所以反文化是因为我们的
culture is so naive about the nature of
文化是如此幼稚的性质
children and that they really have a sin
孩子们，他们真的有一种罪过
nature what is the
本质是什么
rhod well this is the same word that's
很好，这是同一个词
used of a king's scepter and what I
用于国王的权杖和我
decided to do is just give you a quote
决定做的只是给你一个报价
right out of one of the Hebrew books
正是希伯来书中的一本
that I use defining what is a rod so
我使用的定义，什么是如此棒
here's what what they said a rod is in
这就是他们所说的杆所在
Proverbs it's the symbol of discipline
谚语它是纪律的象征
and failure to use the preventive
并且没有使用预防措施
discipline of verbal rebuke and
口头责备和谴责纪律
corrective discipline of physical
物理矫正学科
punishment proverbs says will end in a
惩罚谚语说将结束于
child's death
孩子的死
proverbs warns us about not disciplining
谚语警告我们不要训练
our children so a basic principle I get
我们的孩子这是我得到的基本原则
from this is that discipline is a
从这个是纪律是一个
parental responsibility
父母的责任
so therefore to not discipline my
所以不要管教我的
children is disobedience to the Lord and
孩子不服从主，
that makes a lot of parents
这使得很多 家长
uncomfortable I really don't want to do
不舒服我真的不想做
this and we're gonna talk about the
这个，我们要谈谈
heart later of what could be going on in
心脏后的什么能中回事
the heart of a parent that does not want
父母的心脏不想要的
to discipline their children so hang on
训练他们的孩子如此坚持下去
for that that's 0.5 e we're gonna talk
因为那是0.5 e我们要谈谈
about what's really going on in the
关于什么的真的回事
heart I'm gonna skip over 22:6 that's a
心脏，我要跳过22：6那是一个
famous verse but look at 22 15 the only
着名的诗句，但只看2215
comment I'll make about 22 6 is that you
评论我将约22 6是你
really have to understand what our
真的要了解我们的
Proverbs that proverbs mean generally
谚语一般意味着谚语
speaking this is the way it works it's
说起来这是它的工作方式它
not black and white this is what always
不是黑与白这总是
happens and if you understand proverbs
如果你理解谚语就会发生
that way you get to take a lot of
你采取了很多的办法
pressure off yourself as a parent when
作为父母的时候压力自己
proverbs 22:6 says train up a child in
箴言22：6说要训练一个孩子
the way should go even when he's old he
即使他年纪大了也应该走的路
will not depart from it if that was a
如果那是一个，它将不会离开它
universal black and white teaching of
普及黑白教学
Scripture and not a proverb that would
圣经，而不是一个谚语 会
mean God is a failure as a parent
意味着上帝是一个失败的父母
because God is the perfect parent and
因为上帝是完美的父母和
look at his children and what has
看看他的孩子们有什么
happened with his his children has he
和他的孩子一起发生了他
brought them up in the way that they
领他们在他们的方式
should go and the story of the Old
应该去和老的故事
Testament is that they regularly
遗嘱是他们经常
departed from it so proverbs are
离开它所以谚语是
generally speaking
一般来说
this is how life works look at 22 15
这就是生活的作品怎么看22 15
let's talk about foolishness for a
让我们来谈谈愚蠢的
moment foolishness is bound up in the
时刻的愚蠢被束缚在了
heart of a child but the rod of
一个孩子的心，但杆
discipline will remove it far from him
纪律将远离他
what is this foolishness here's what the
这里的愚蠢是什么？
Hebrew word means morally deficient
希伯来语意味着道德上缺乏
lacking sense some translated this and I
缺乏感觉一些翻译了这个和我
can just kind of chuckled when I saw
我看到的时候可以轻笑一下
this thick-headed can you relate to that
这个小笨蛋，你能理解
either with yourself or with your child
与自己或与您的孩子
we can be awful thick-headed foolishness
我们可能是可怕的愚蠢的愚蠢
morally deficient lacks sense a word
道德缺乏缺乏理智一句话
that came up regularly as I was doing
我经常这样做
the word study on this was insolence
对此研究这个词是无礼的
which would be more purposeful rebellion
这将是更有目的的反叛
insolence and that's important when we
傲慢，这对我们来说很重要
come back to the question of do you
回到你的问题
always use spanking they always use
总是使用他们总是使用的打屁股
spanking and I'll give you an answer to
打屁股，我会给你一个答案
that in just a few minutes but one of
在短短几分钟内，但只有一个
the questions that would come up in my
我的问题会出现
mind is is it insolence is there
头脑是它是无礼的
rebellion direct rebellion going on so a
叛乱直接叛乱正在发生
basic principle here children are not
这里基本原则儿童不是
naturally wise but proverbs would say
自然明智但谚语会说
they're the simple-minded or maybe the
他们是笨笨的，也许是傻瓜
scoffer or maybe the full and I need to
嘲笑或者可能是我需要的全部
be disciple
做门徒
disciplining them toward wisdom as the
把他们当作智慧训练
book of Proverbs would teach let's look
箴言书会教我们看
at chapter 23 verses 13 and 14 and see
在第23章13和14节看到
the discipline is an act of love do not
纪律是一种爱的行为
hold back discipline from the child
阻止孩子的纪律
although you beat him with the rod he
虽然你用杆殴打他
will not die you shall beat him with the
不会死的你会用它来打败他
rod and deliver his soul from Sheol
从阴间拯救他的灵魂
it is loving to discipline our children
它很爱纪律我们的孩子
how loving is it to allow a child to
如何让孩子有爱心
just grow up their own way as our
我们只是以自己的方式成长
culture would say just be whatever you
文化会说不管你是什么
want to be
想成为
but if you really believe there is a sin
但如果你真的相信有罪
nature that's going on on the inside and
在里面发生的自然
we just allow our children to be
我们只是让我们的孩子是
whatever they want to be how loving is
无论他们想要多么有爱心
that the wisdom of Scripture would be
圣经的智慧就是这样
give direction shape your children one
给方向塑造你的孩子一个
of the commentaries on this verse said
对这节经文的评论说
this a remedy for correction is the rod
这个纠正的补救措施是杆
of discipline in order to drive the
纪律以驱动
foolishness from him one must keep in
他必须保持愚蠢
mind that this discipline is important
请注意，这门学科很重要
to curb moral insolence that might lead
遏制可能导致的道德傲慢
and turn to rebellion against God I
转向反对上帝的叛逆我
don't want my child to be in jail
不要让我的孩子入狱
someday so I'm gonna do the best I can
总有一天，我会尽我所能
to shape his or her character in
塑造他或她的性格中
conclusion with proverbs chapter 29
谚语第29章的结论
verse 15 another very clear passage the
第15节另一个非常明确的段落
rod and reproof give wisdom but a child
杖和责备给予智慧但是孩子
who gets his own way brings shame to his
谁走自己的路让他感到羞耻
mother isn't that so true just we see it
只要我们看到它，母亲就不是那么真实
happening over and over in our culture
发生一遍又一遍在我们的文化
now that leads us to Ephesians 6 as
现在，这导致我们成为以弗所书6
we're looking at key passages so
我们正在寻找关键段落
Ephesians chapter 6 and I told you we
以弗所书第6章，我告诉过你们
would talk about the phrase nurture and
会谈论培育和
admonition and then in this passage we
告诫然后在这段经文中我们
need to especially talk about the phrase
需要特别谈谈这句话
do not provoke your children to anger as
不要惹儿女的气如
we continue to shape our thinking about
我们将继续塑造我们的思维左右
biblical discipline so context talked
圣经学科所以上下文谈了
about that the last time Christ is the
关于基督是最后一次
head of his body the church now live
教会现在住在他身体的头上
like it live like he is your head
喜欢它就像他是你的头一样生活
children here's how you do it verse 1
这里的孩子们就是这样做的第1节
children if you're gonna live as if
孩子，如果你要活得好像
Christ is the head of your life obey
基督是 你生命服从 的头
your parents in the Lord for this is
你父母在主里面就是这样
right that's and that word right means
这是正确的，这个词是正确的意思
it's the righteous thing to do father's
做父亲是正义的事
how do you live as if Christ is your
你是如何生活的，好像基督是你的
head he's the head of his body the
他是他身体的头部
church now how do you walk in a manner
教堂现在你怎么走路的方式
that
那
worthy of your calling fathers here's
值得你在这里打电话的父亲
what you do don't provoke your children
你做什么不会激怒你的孩子
to anger but bring them up so you're
愤怒，但他们带来了所以你
it's has direction toward maturity
它有朝着成熟的方向发展
implied in it bring them up in the
隐含在它里面
discipline and instruction of the Lord
主的训练和指导
or nurture and admonition of the Lord
或主的训诫和训诫
real quickly definitions of those words
真正快速定义那些词
discipline or training and then that
纪律或训练然后
second word admonition you've over the
第二个字告诫你已经过了
last three months heard this word a
最近三个月听到这个词了
number of times the national association
次全国性协会数
of new thetac counselors that's the word
新的thetac辅导员就是这个词
new 'the new Thessia the discipline and
新的'新的Thessia的纪律和
instruction of the lord the warning and
主的 指示 警告和
the best passage or the best book I can
我能做的最好的一段或最好的书
think of of what does this mean to bring
想一想这意味着什么
your children up in the discipline and
你的孩子在纪律和
instruction it's loving instruction of
指导它是爱的指导
parents who want to give loving guidance
想要给予爱心指导的父母
to their children and it's the book of
给他们的孩子， 这是他们的书
Proverbs where the father is saying my
父亲在说我的谚语
son my son my son just over and over
儿子我的儿子我的儿子一遍又一遍
trying to give direction to his children
试图给方向给他的孩子
that's the implication of this word new
这就是新词的含义
Thessia discipline and instruction of
Thessia纪律与教学
the Lord now let's talk about do not
主现在让我们谈谈不要
exasperate that's what the NIV says or
令人恼火的是NIV所说的或者
do not provoke your children to anger
不要激怒你的孩子
then I found this delightful list from
然后我从中找到了这个令人愉快的清单
John MacArthur's book successful
约翰麦克阿瑟的书成功了
Christian parenting on what are ways
基督徒养育的方式是什么
that you can exasperate your children
你可以激怒你的孩子
but the word literally means this or the
但字面意思是这个或那个
phrase make resentful to provoke to
短语让人怨恨
provoke to anger or go to anger so to
引起愤怒或愤怒
make angry do not exasperate or make
生气不要恼怒或制造
angry or go to your children what are
生气或去找你的孩子是什么
some ways that we can exasperate our
我们可以通过一些方式来激怒我们
children well think back with your
孩子们好好回想一下
parents do you ever feel like one God
父母，你有没有觉得自己像一个上帝
somebody got better treatment than you
有人得到了比你更好的待遇
did and that just bothered you to no end
做了，那只是困扰你到最后
as a child that somebody was the
作为一个孩子，有人是
favorite in the family and I would think
在家庭中最喜欢的，我会想
that this would be really difficult
这将是非常困难
called in our culture and we need to be
在我们的文化中呼唤，我们需要
warning parents that are where there's
警告那些有父母的父母
stuff children that it would be so easy
孩子们会觉得这么容易
to show favorites of one child over the
显示一个孩子的最爱
other anger unrealistic expectations I'm
其他愤怒不切实际的期望我
not going to comment on all these just a
不打算评论所有这些只是一个
few going down through here over
很少有人经过这里
protection we hear this from children
保护我们从孩子那里听到这个
give me some space you know just let me
给我一些你知道的空间让我
grow up give me some freedom let me
长大后给我一些自由让我
breathe
呼吸
we have a phrase that we use on our
我们有一个我们用的短语
campus and even other campuses use that
校园甚至其他校园都使用它
are using this in recent years we call
我们称之为近年来使用这个
the parent that is just always there
那个永远在那里的父母
with their child with their college
和他们的孩子一起上大学
student we call them helicopter parents
学生我们称他们为直升机父母
they're always hovering over their
他们总是徘徊在他们的身上
children even college students give me
孩子甚至大学生都给我
some space
一些空间
let me breathe I'll comment more on that
让我呼吸， 我会对此发表更多评论
in a little bit because we've had some
在一 点点，因为我们已经有一些
cases in recent years with parents not
近年来与父母没有的案件
and children of adult or parents of
和成人或父母的孩子
adult children not agreeing with their
成年子女不同意他们的意见
child's choice of a spouse and there's
孩子对配偶的选择就在那里
been some really sad stories that have
曾经是一些非常悲伤的故事
come out of that in in recent years of
近年来问世的，在
parents not going to their kids wedding
父母不要去他们的孩子婚礼
and things like that just lots of pain
之类的东西，只是很多痛苦
neglect number-6 little or no
忽略数字6很少或没有
relationship with the child that can
与孩子的关系可以
exasperate a child you can think through
激怒你可以思考的孩子
all the these others and dr. MacArthur
所有这些人和博士。麦克阿瑟
has the details in his book successful
他书中的细节成功了
Christian parenting now let's think why
基督教养育现在让我们思考为什么
would a parent not want to discipline a
父母不想纪律吗？
child and we have to take that right
孩子，我们必须采取正确的态度
back to the heart of what's going on in
回到正在发生的事情的核心
the heart of the parent so let's review
父母的心脏让我们回顾一下
the heart a little bit and let me remind
心有点让我提醒
you of two key verses proverbs 4:23 in
你有两个关键经文谚语4:23 in
Hebrews 4:12 we won't look at them if
希伯来书4:12 如果，我们不会看他们
you were here the last month we talked
你在这里谈论我们的最后一个月
about the heart in a little bit of
关于心脏的一点点
detail proverbs 4:23 says guard your
细节箴言4:23说守护你的
heart
心
for from it flow the issues of life and
从中流出生命和问题
then Hebrews 4:12 the last phrase says
然后希伯来书4:12最后一句话说
your heart has thoughts and intentions
你的心有想法和意图
so what might be the thoughts and
那可能是什么想法和
intentions of the heart that's
内心的意图
influencing the parents hearts and
影响父母的心，
they're living out of that as proverbs
他们的生活就像谚语一样
4:23 says out of it are flowing the
4:23 说它正在流动
springs of life so the way I'm dealing
生命的泉源，所以我正在处理的方式
with my children it's ultimately coming
和我的孩子一起，它最终会来临
from my heart so what is the heart it
从我的心里，它的内心是什么
has to do with my motives my drives my
与我的动机有关，我的动力是我的
wants desires as we just saw the last
我们只是看到最后一个想要欲望
time Matthew 6 treasures where your
时间马太6宝藏你的地方
treasure is there your heart will be
珍惜在你心中
also what are you treasuring so what
你还珍惜什么呢？
could be going on first of all some
可能会首先进行一些
extremes to avoid we obviously don't
极端，以避免我们显然没有
want to be the overly permissive parent
想成为过度宽容的父母
cultures full of those verses the overly
文化充满了过分的那些经文
controlling parent seem plenty of those
控制父母似乎很多
too same thing as saying the overly
和过分说话太相同了
indulgent parent versus the overly
放纵父母与过分
protective parent and I just want to I
保护父母，我只想要我
have to insert a comment here and I'm
要在这里插入一个评论 ，我
gonna be a little critical of
要成为一个小的临界
homeschooling and I've earned a right to
在家上学，我有权获得
do that because I'm in my 19th year of
这样做是因为我已经19岁了
homeschooling here's a tendency I've
在家上学这是我的一种倾向
seen in homeschooling is that we think
在家庭教育中看到的是我们的想法
as homeschooling parents that we can
作为家庭教育的父母，我们可以
erect walls high enough to keep the
竖立墙壁足够高，以保持
world away from our children and there
从我们的孩子世界的距离，有
is great naivety in that you know why
因为你知道为什么，这是天真的
because they have the world already
因为他们已经拥有了世界
inside of them scripture says they have
在他们里面， 经文说他们有
a sin nature we have a tendency to be
罪性，我们有一种倾向是
overly protective now what are some
过度保护现在有些什么
common heart themes well there's the
常见的心脏主题很好
comfort loving heart
舒适爱心
what would a comfort loving heart sound
什么是舒适的爱心声
like or what might go through your mind
喜欢或者可能会在你的脑海中发生什么
I think I'll pretend like I didn't see
我想我会假装我没有看到
that it's a little bit inconvenient
这有点不方便
right now I really don't want to deal
现在我真的不想处理
with this right now so I didn't really
与此 所以我现在真的不
see my child do that I don't really feel
看到我的孩子那样做， 我真的不觉得
like dealing with that right now that
就像现在处理那样
could be a comfort loving
可能是一个舒适的爱
heart now the difference is gonna be if
心脏现在差异将是如果
you know that's your tendency the
你知道这是你的倾向吗？
difference is gonna be you might have
差异就是你可能会有的
that tendency and you know you have that
这种倾向，你知道你有那个
tendency and you say I know I have that
倾向，你说我知道我有那个
tendency and I'm still gonna discipline
倾向，我仍然要纪律
my child that would be the godly
我的孩子，这将是虔诚的
response to any of these the controlling
响应任何这些控制
heart might say I will beat you into
心脏可能会说我会打败你进入
submission
服从
boy what does that lead to that sounds
男孩是什么导致这种声音
like a rebellious teen in the making a
就像一个反叛的青少年在制作一个
parent who's just really aggressive and
父母谁真的很有侵略性
beating the child you'll do what I want
击败孩子你会做我想做的事
you to do even if I have to force you to
即使我不得不强迫你去做
do it
做到这一点
a people-pleasing heart I really want my
一个让人赏心悦目的心， 我真的很想要我
children to like me I just want my
孩子们喜欢我，我只想要我的
children to be my friends
孩子是我的朋友
I'm afraid my children won't like me of
我担心我的孩子不会喜欢我
course obviously nothing wrong with
当然显然没有错
wanting your children to like you but if
希望你的孩子喜欢你， 但如果
that's the primary motivation you're
这是你的主要动机
gonna have a hard time disciplining your
要训练你的时间会很困难
children we have to be motivated by love
孩子， 我们必须受到爱的激励
that my child needs to be shaped because
我的孩子需要塑造因为
they have a sin nature and I'm trying to
他们有罪性，我正在努力
make a disciple so I'm gonna do what my
做一个门徒，所以我会做我的
heart doesn't want me to do and I'm
心不想要我做，我是
gonna discipline my child the pleasure
要训​​练我的孩子快乐
loving heart this is no fun I think I'll
爱心这不好玩我想我会的
just ignore this right now what
现在就忽略这一点
Scripture would seem to imply is this if
圣经似乎暗示这是否如此
you don't want to deal with these things
你不想处理这些事情
you don't really love your children in
你真的不爱你的孩子在
that what proverbs said that if I just
什么谚语说，如果我只是
allow my child to grow up and I don't
允许我的孩子长大，我没有
deal with my child and discipline my
与我的孩子打交道并训练我的孩子
child I'm not loving my child I've known
孩子我不爱我的孩子我知道
quite a few adult men that I've
我有很多成年男子
counseled and boy did I wish they had
劝告和男孩，我希望他们有
never had children they just did not
从来没有孩子，他们只是没有
want to take responsibility for their
我们要为自己负责
children I just wish they would have
孩子我只是希望他们有
never even have had children to begin
从来没有孩子开始
with some general guidelines for all
为所有人提供一些一般性指导
forms of discipline you are not hearing
你没有听到的纪律形式
me say that we're spanking all the time
我说我们一直在打屁股
aren't you relieved to hear that not
听到这个没有，你不是松了一口气
spanking all the time whatever the
什么时候打屁股
discipline is that we're using here's
纪律是我们在这里使用的
just some general guidelines and after I
只是一些一般的指导方针和我之后
was reviewing this today I realized I
今天正在审查这个我意识到我
left a very important when off and my
离开的时候离我很重要
wife will laugh when she realizes when
当她意识到的时候，妻子会笑
she hears the one that I left off the
她听到了我离开的那个
list because this one was really
列表因为这个真的
important to us but let's go down
对我们很重要，但让我们走下去
through these some general guidelines
通过这些一般指导方针
for all forms of discipline never in
所有从来没有在形式的纪律
anger my kids always knew something was
愤怒我的孩子们总是知道什么是
up when I'd say meet me in my bedroom or
当我说要在我的卧室或我的房子里见到我的时候
go to my bedroom sometimes I didn't join
有时我没去加入我的卧室
them right away because I needed to calm
他们马上因为我需要冷静
down
下
first well there's nothing like your
首先，没有什么比你更好了
anger that's gonna get you in trouble
愤怒会让你陷入困境
when it comes to disciplining your
当涉及到训练你的
children we never discipline in anger we
孩子们，我们从不在愤怒中训练我们
must be controlled because here's why
必须加以控制， 因为这就是原因
not only because it violates Scripture
不仅因为它违反了圣经
with anger but because discipline is
愤怒，但因为纪律是
about discipleship how can you be
关于门徒训练你怎么样？
discipled if you've lost your temper
如果你发脾气，就要训练
remember Ephesians 4:29 why don't we
记得以弗所书4:29 我们为什么不
look at that Ephesians 4:29 wonderful
看看以弗所书4:29太棒了
verse for us to remember as parents
我们要记住作为父母的经文
nothing like harsh critical words that
没有像严厉的批评性言论那样
can be crushing to a child Ephesians
可以粉碎给以弗所人的孩子
4:29 says let no unwholesome word
4:29说不要说不好听的话
proceed from your mouth but only such a
从你的口开始， 但只有这样的
word as is good for edification
这个词有益于教化
according to the need of the moment that
根据当下的需要
it may give grace to those who hear
它可能会给那些听到的人带来恩惠
watching our speech as parents see the
看着父母看到我们的演讲
goal is the gospel so if I'm making the
目标是福音，所以如果我做了
heart the target and the child is
目标和孩子的心脏
understanding his or her desires after a
了解后，他或她的欲望
while they're gonna begin to see they
而他们会开始看到他们
have unruly desires so the goal is the
有不守规矩的欲望所以目标是
gospel we want our children to know or
福音，我们希望我们的孩子知道或
realize and be desperate for a savior
意识到并渴望一个救世主
know and realize their hearts and be
知道并认识到自己的心灵
desperate for a savior a lot could be
绝望的救世主了很多可能是
said about this but let me just tell you
对此说了但是我告诉你
a story
一个故事
about four or five years ago I think it
大约四五年前我认为
was now there was a time with our
我们现在有一段时间了
youngest child where it just seemed like
最小的孩子，它似乎就像
almost every day I was having to address
几乎每天我都要解决
something in her life and I was
她生活中的一些事情，我
determined that it was this was going to
确定它是这个打算
be discipleship and I wanted her to
是门徒，我想要她
understand her heart so I kept asking
了解她的心，所以我一直在问
her the same questions what were you
她同样的问题， 什么是你
wanting that you're not getting and what
想要你没有得到什么
are you getting that you're not wanting
你得到的是你不想要的吗？
and it was over a period of days and may
这是一段时间，可能
even have been a couple of weeks I'm
甚至已经有几个星期 我
losing track of time now and we got to
现在失去了时间，我们得到了
another discipline instance I called her
我打电话给她的另一个学科实例
into the room yet another time what are
进入房间又一次是什么
you wanting that you're not getting what
你想要你没有得到什么
are you getting that you're not wanting
你得到的是你不想要的吗？
and she said something like this this is
她说这是这样的
somewhat of a paraphrase I was trying to
有些意译，我想的
reconstruct exactly what she said but
完全重建她说的话但是
I'm not remembering the details but it
我不记得细节，但它
was something like this dad I'm just so
就像这个爸爸我就是这样
frustrated with myself I can't do
对自己感到沮丧，我做不到
anything right
什么都对
I am so selfish and I thought we're
我很自私，我以为我们是
getting somewhere
到了某个地方
and I was able to go into the gospel of
我能够进入福音
it honey this is why Jesus died on the
它蜂蜜这就是为什么耶稣在死
cross for you he not only died for our
为你而十字架他不仅为我们而死
bad behavior he died for our sin nature
他为我们的罪性而死的坏行为
our selfishness that night she asked the
那天晚上她问我们的自私
Lord Jesus to be her Savior she
主耶稣是她的救主
understood she grew up in a home hearing
了解她在家庭听证会上长大
about sin
关于罪
she knew sin as bad things we do she
她知道罪是我们做的坏事
knew she grew up with a biblical
知道她长大了圣经
counselor as a dad she heard about heart
辅导员作为一个爸爸，她听说过心脏
motives regularly I feel sorry for my
经常有动机我为我感到难过
kids hearing about heart motives all the
孩子们听到所有的心脏动机
time she heard about that but that night
那个时候她听说过那个晚上
she owned it I am selfish and she
她拥有它我是自私的她
understood in a new way her need of a
以一种新的方式理解她需要一个
savior that's our goal
救世主是我们的目标
this discipline is about the gospel
这个学科是关于福音的
we're pointing them toward the Savior
我们把它们指向救主
why do they need why did Jesus
他们为什么需要耶稣呢？
have to die d not everything is a major
有芯片D并非一切是一个重大的
issue some of you really need to hear
问题你们中的一些人真的需要听到
this and your some of your council
这和你的一些议会
leaves really need to hear this we can
叶子真的需要听到这个我们可以
be so frustrated with life in general
对生活如此沮丧
and all of our own frustrations that
以及我们所有的挫败感
everything that our children do is a
我们孩子所做的一切都是
major issue not everything is a major
重大问题不是一切都是专业
issue e
问题e
discipline issues are discipleship
纪律问题是门徒训练
opportunities with the heart as the
与心脏的机会
target I'm gonna suggest some questions
目标我会提出一些问题
for you to ask children or to teach your
为了你问孩子或教你的
counsel ease to ask children to turn
律师轻松地要求孩子们转身
them into discipleship opportunities and
他们进入门徒训练的机会和
that goes back to the principle again of
可以追溯到的原则再次
active parenthood not passive Parenthood
积极的父母不是被动的父母
this next one has been extremely
下一个是极端的
important to us rules without
没有对我们很重要规则
relationship leads to rebellion we need
关系导致我们需要的反叛
to have rules but be heavy on
有规则，但要沉重
relationship heavy on relationship lots
关系很重的关系
and lots of rules with no relationship
和许多没有关系的规则
leads to rebellion another key principle
导致反叛的另一个关键原则
remember justice what is justice about
记住正义什么是正义
Lady Justice and what's she holding in
正义女士和她抱着什么
her hands scales God is a God of justice
她的手秤上帝是一个正义之神
this sin equals this punishment
这罪是等于这种惩罚
what is equitable for this offense of
什么是这种罪行的公平
the child it's not always spanking this
孩子并不总是打屁股
equals this you can't control yourself
等于你，你无法控制自己
on the computer so you're losing this
在电脑上，你就失去了这个
computer time equitable punishment for
计算机时间公平惩罚
sin justice what is equitable punishment
罪的正义是什么是公平的惩罚
next point it in other words it doesn't
下一个点它，换句话说，它不
always have to be spanking H deal with
总是要打屁股打交道
issues as quickly as possible it's just
问题尽快它只是
a general principle of Scripture related
圣经相关的一般原则
to conflict resolution that things
解决冲突，事情
should be dealt with quickly forgiveness
应该快速处理宽恕
and reconciliation should always happen
和解应该永远发生
at least from the parents
至少来自父母
perspective you can't control what's
透视你无法控制什么
going on in your child's heart but we
继续你孩子的心脏，但我们
want to be reconciled after this process
希望在这个过程之后得到和解
is over
结束了
remember to appeal to the conscience so
记得如此呼吁良心
questions like what would the Lord want
像主想要的那些问题
you to do what would make Jesus happy
你要做的事会让耶稣快乐
what are you wanting we're going for
你想要什么我们想要的
something deeper we're appealing to the
更深层次的东西我们很有吸引力
conscience this is not just about
良心这不仅仅是关于
behavior modification so how do you turn
行为修改所以你怎么转
these month times of discipline into
这些月的纪律进入
discipleship here's some questions that
这里门徒的一些问题，
we use these type of questions and I
我们使用这些类型的问题和我
used to have an order for these but I
我曾经订购过这些订单
for the last couple of weeks as I've
在过去的几周里，我一直都是
been preparing I was trying to remember
一直在准备我试图记住
my order that I'd go through these with
我的订单，我将通过这些
the kids and I just couldn't reconstruct
孩子们，我无法重建
it but it it was these questions I
它， 但这是我的问题
wanted to get the facts what did you do
我想知道你做了什么
what were you wanting what is it you
你想要的是什么？
didn't want what should you have done
我不想要你做了什么
what do you deserve what are you gonna
你应该得到什么？
do the next time those questions gave me
下次那些问题给我做了
wonderful opportunities to disciple the
门徒的绝佳机会
kids rather than it just being an act of
孩子而不仅仅是一种行为
discipline then here's the one I forgot
纪律然后这是我忘了的那个
prompt obedience we had a statement that
提示服从我们有一个声明
any of our kids I'd I would be
我的任何一个孩子， 我都会
absolutely shocked if we just randomly
如果我们随机的话，绝对震惊
called one of the kids right now and
现在 叫一个孩子
started this sentence any one of our
开始这句话中的任何一个 我们
kids would be able to finish it to delay
孩子们将能够完成它推迟
is to disobey we drilled that into our
是不服从我们钻进我们的
children here's why here's the
这里的孩子就是为什么这里的
motivation do we want our children to be
我们希望自己的孩子成为动力
lazy followers of Christ or do we want
懒惰的基督信徒或我们想要的人
them to be diligent followers of Christ
他们是基督的勤奋信徒
do we want them to have the attitude
我们希望他们有这种态度吗？
that well I can just kind of get around
好吧，我可以解决这个问题
to obeying the Lord whenever I feel like
每当我想要时服从主
it well what am i doing as a parent am i
我作为父母在做什么呢？
creating an environment where it's okay
创造一个可以接受的环境
to put off obedience to parents and just
推迟服从父母和公正
kind of have the attitude of well I'll
我的态度很好
get there I'll get around to it to let
到那儿我会绕过它让它
to delay is to disobey or think about
延迟就是不服从或思考
their future
他们的未来
if if they say to their boss somewhere
如果他们在某个地方对他们的老板说
down the road the boss says I'd like you
老板说我喜欢你
to do this okay hold on second
要做到这一点好吧坚持第二
what's the boss going to think are a lot
老板会想的是什么
of bosses gonna think to delay is to
老板会想到延迟就是
disobey this next chart that's in your
不服从你的下一张图表
notes has been a really shaping chart
笔记是一个真正的塑造图表
for me the difference between being an
对我来说，成为一个
authoritative parent and an
权威的父母和
authoritarian parent I can tell you lots
专制的父母， 我可以告诉你很多
of horror stories about authoritarian
关于威权主义的恐怖故事
parents dictatorial parents the instead
相反，父母是独裁父母
of the sea the authority line and how
海权威 线，以及如何
it's going down
它正在下降
the authoritarian parent wants that to
专制的父母希望这样做
remain the same until their child is
保持不变，直到他们的孩子
married and maybe even after the child's
结婚， 甚至可能在孩子之后
married and they're out of the home I
结婚了，他们离开了我的家
think the wise parent realizes that
认为聪明的父母意识到这一点
through the years my authority is going
多年来， 我的权威正在进行
down now I'll just give you a real
现在，我只会给你一个真实的
practical example of that all three of
所有三个的实际例子
my boys are bigger than me and I am glad
我的男孩比我大，我很高兴
they respect me the last time I tried to
他们最后一次尝试时都尊重我
wrestle my youngest son I ended up with
摔跤我最小的儿子，我结束了
a sore back for two weeks and I'm
疼了两个星期，我
embarrassed to say that my youngest son
不好意思地说我最小的儿子
can now beat me arm wrestling don't tell
现在能打败我的手臂摔跤不说
him I said that my influence better be
他说我的影响力更好
going up as my authority is going down
我的权威正在下降
they're bigger than me I can't fight
他们比我大，我无法战斗
them there's no way I'm gonna force them
他们没有办法强迫他们
into submission right now so they they
现在提交给他们他们
obey because they respect me my
服从因为他们尊重我
authority has gone down and don't get
权威已经下降，没有得到
too technical about the crossing point
关于过境点太技术化了
there and you're going okay is that age
在那里，你会好起来的是那个年龄
13 is that age 14 that's not the point
13岁是14岁，这不是重点
the point is that you're sensing that at
问题是 ，你感应，在
some point your influence is increasing
有一点你的影响正在增加
as your Authority is going down
因为你的管理局正在倒塌
lots of relationship rules without
很多关系规则没有
relationship leads to rebellion
关系导致反叛
what are we raising our children
我们养育孩子的是什么
remember scripture says bring them up in
记得圣经说要把它们带进来
the nurture and admonition of the Lord
主的培养和训诫
so we're raising our children to be
所以我们要养育孩子
independent adults not dependent on you
独立的成年人不依赖于你
the rest of their lives now that leads
现在，他们的余生都是领先的
us then after all these general
然后，我们毕竟这些一般
principles - what do we do about
原则- 我们该怎么做
spanking notice the phrase that I'm
打屁股注意我的短语
using and I got this from a secular
使用， 我从世俗中得到了这个
sociologist and I'm gonna start using it
社会学家，我将开始使用它
because our culture so many in our
因为我们的文化在我们这么多
culture are so bent on getting rid of
文化是如此倾向于摆脱
spanking that I think we need to start
我认为我们需要开始打屁股
using some qualifiers like conditional
使用像条件一样的限定符
spanking and that comes right from us an
打屁股，来自我们
unbeliever who believes in spanking and
不信的人谁相信打屁股
he calls a conditional spanking
他称之为有条件的打屁股
what's the legality right now in
什么是现在的合法性
California here's the summary for you
加州这里是你的总结
and then you have a whole handout that
然后你有一个完整的讲义
looks like this it's an appendix to your
看起来是这样的它是一个附录到您
notes which is the Attorney General's
注释是司法部长的
opinion from the state of California I
来自加州I的状态意见
got this from a lawyer who's a biblical
从一位圣经的律师那里得到了这个
counselor and he said here's basically
辅导员，他说这基本上是
what's going on in Cal in LA County
在洛杉矶县的Cal发生了什么
right now here's what's going on
现在这里是怎么回事
so maybe make that a note in your in
所以也许在你的里面做个便条
your notes this is LA County this is the
您的笔记，这是洛杉矶县，这 是
climate right now not the rest of the
气候现在不是 其余
state of California that shouldn't
加利福尼亚州不应该
surprise us right it's not currently
让我们感到惊讶， 现在不是
illegal however it is seriously frowned
然而非法非常皱眉
upon a social worker may try to take
对社会工作者可能会尝试采取
your children or even prosecute you on
你的孩子，甚至起诉你
the issue but I gave you the Attorney
这个问题， 但我给了你律师
General's opinion so you know what the
将军的意见让你知道了什么
Attorney General says and he says that
司法部长说，他说
if it's done properly it is not against
如果它做得好，就不会反对
the law some social workers may be more
法律一些社会工作者可能更多
tolerant of parents rights but as a
容忍父母的权利，但作为一个
general matter they tend to see children
一般来说， 他们往往会看到孩子
as belonging to the state or at least
为属于所述状态或至少
believing that they have greater wisdom
相信他们有更大的智慧
in childcare than any parent and that
在育儿比任何父母和
was the opinion of a lawyer so do we
是律师的意见，我们也是
always spank in the answer's no here was
总是在答案中打屁股没有
my guideline
我的指南
was it direct disobedience was it
在它直接抗命是它
rebellious so for example I asked a
反叛，所以例如我问了一个
child to do something and a son looks at
孩子做一些事情，儿子看
me and says no that's gonna get a
我并且说不，那会得到一个
spanking
拍击
I saved spanking for serious offenses
我为严重的罪行保存了打屁股
there were other than that it was well
除此以外，它还不错
what equals this crime justice this
什么等于这种犯罪正义
equals this this type of rebellion or
等于这种类型的反叛或
this type of behavior gets this type of
这种类型的行为得到这种类型的
discipline how about the hand or other
训练手或其他如何
instrument
仪器
this is opinion I'll tell you my
这是我会告诉你的意见
preference and it's because scripture
偏好，这是因为经文
says a rod that I would use some other
我会用其他的一根杆子说
instrument other than the hand many
仪器以外的手很多
people say the implication of this would
人们说这意味着什么
be that the hand is reserved for love
是为爱而保留的
and some other instrument then is used
然后使用其他一些工具
for discipline the instrument that I
为了训练我的乐器
used was a little wooden spoon that was
所用的是一个小木勺，这是
notorious in our family tell you a funny
我们家里臭名昭着告诉你一个好笑的
story about the rod in our family back
我们家里的棒子的故事
in the day when we would wear ties and
在 我们穿领带的 那一天
coats to church if I wanted my children
如果我想要我的孩子，可以去教堂
to behave when we were trying to get
当我们想要得到时表现
them to sit still in church I would just
他们会静静地坐在教堂里
pack the wooden spoon inside my coat
把木勺装在我的外套里面
pocket and as the boys would have a case
口袋里和男孩们会有一个案子
of what we called the wiggle worms all I
我所谓的摆动蠕虫我
had to do was look down the row and
需要做的就是往下看行
flashed the spoon
闪过勺子
it was amazing the magic that that
这真是太神奇了
caused how old or how young here's one
导致这里的年龄或年龄有多大
thing that we found out and I can't
我们发现的东西，我不能
answer this in detail if you want to
如果你愿意，可以详细解答这个问题
talk about this afterwards just come
刚谈到这件事后才来
talk to us but here's the principle that
跟我们说说，但这是原则
I and I've read this with others and we
我和我和其他人一起读过这篇文章
certainly found it to be true in our
我们当然发现它是真实的
home that if we were consistent in
家，如果我们在一致
disciplining preschoolers rarely during
在学期间很少训练学龄前儿童
the elementary years did we have to
我们必须这些基本年份
spank and I can't ever remember spanking
打屁股，我不记得打屁股
a teenager my wife could correct me if
一个少年， 我的妻子可以纠正我，如果
I'm wrong on that but we just boy by the
我错了，但我们只是在男孩旁边
time age five or six was rolling around
五六岁的时间滚来滚去
we were just seeing that the need for
我们只是看到了需要
that type of discipline was just going
这种类型的纪律刚刚开始
downhill
下坡
every so often during the elementary
小学期间经常这么做
years something very serious arose that
年有严重的事出现了这
we had to use that type of discipline
我们必须使用这种类型的纪律
but not not very often do we have to
但 我们不得不经常这样做
spank let's just ask the question
打屁股让我们问问题
bluntly the answer biblically is yes
直截了当地回答圣经是肯定的
I've got a quote for you from
我有一个报价给你
shepherding your child's heart from Ted
从泰德牧养你的孩子的心脏
Tripps parental handbook he says this we
Tripps父母手册他说这个我们
do not employ the rod of Correction
不要使用矫正杆
because we looked at our child and
因为我们看着我们的孩子和
decide decided what this child needs is
决定这孩子需要的是什么
a good spanking
一个很好的打屁股
we use the rod of Correction because God
我们使用纠正的杖因为上帝
reveals truth to parents and says what
向父母揭示真相并说出了什么
your child needs is a good spanking the
你的孩子需要的是一个很好的打屁股
rod of Correction is a response of
纠正的杆是一个回应
obedience and faith on the part of a
服从和信心上的部分
parent the parent is trusting God who
父母是父母信任上帝的人
has said that the rod of Correction will
曾经说过，纠错的杆将
be the means through which children will
是通过哪些孩子会
escape the folly that is bound up in
摆脱束缚的愚蠢
their hearts so what we have to decide
他们的心所以我们必须决定
beloved is are we going to allow the
良人我们要允许
philosophy of our world to guide us or
我们的世界哲学指导我们或
are we going to be guided by a biblical
我们是否会受到圣经的引导
philosophy of parenting so some basic
育儿哲学如此基本
guidelines about spanking in conclusion
有关结论打屁股指南
it's never just about a spanking please
请不要只打屁股
draw it into your
把它画进你的
sciples your your counsel ease it's
sciples 你对你的律师缓解它的
about discipleship it's not just
关于门徒训练， 这不仅仅是
behavior modification we're going after
行为修改我们正在追求
the heart we want to disciple our
我们想要训练我们的心
children
孩子
you need to stay controlled go cool down
你需要保持控制冷静下来
if necessary in private so you're not
如果有必要私下，所以你不是
humiliating the child in front of others
在别人面前羞辱孩子
and especially Wow don't do it if you're
特别是哇 ，如果你这样 做，不要这样做
in public that just wouldn't be wise
在公共场合，这是不明智的
what it we have a friend who won't use
我们有一个不会使用的朋友
the word spanking but his in public
打屁股，但他的公开
especially he believes spanked and
特别是他相信打屁股
spanking his children but he's trained
打他的孩子，但他受过训练
his children they call spanking a
他的孩子们打电话打屁股
reminder and so when they're out of the
提醒等，当他们出来的
grocery store and the child's
杂货店和孩子的
misbehaving all Z has to do you can't
行为不端所有Z必须做你不能
say spanking publicly anymore so what he
再说公开打屁股了，所以他
says is he looks at his child and says
他说是看着他的孩子说的
do you want to remind her and they know
你想提醒她，他们知道吗？
exactly what that means
究竟是什么意思
make sure your reasons are clear
确保你的理由清楚
remember the questions before I tried to
在我尝试之前记住这些问题
go through those questions every time I
每次我都会经历这些问题
was disciplining a child and then swats
正在训练一个孩子，然后拍打
that sting the rear end every so often
每隔一段时间就刺穿后端
I'd have a child that regret regretted
我有一个后悔后悔的孩子
and said regretted it later and said try
后来说后悔并说试试
to make me cry you can guess that was a
让我哭泣你可以猜到那是一个
boy we have one that loaded his pants
男孩，我们有一个装裤子
with magazines before he went to my
在他去我的 杂志之前和杂志
bedroom
卧室
like do I have stupid written on my head
就像我写在我头上的傻瓜一样
another time that same child said to me
另一次，同一个孩子对我说
that didn't hurt okay why why do we want
没有伤害好的为什么我们为什么要这样做
it to sting because the wages of sin is
因为罪 的工资是吝啬的
death we want to associate sin with pain
死亡我们想把罪与痛苦联系起来
and then afterwards there's forgiveness
然后是宽恕
often we would finish with a prayer of
通常我们会以祈祷结束
them asking the Lord for forgiveness for
他们要求主宽恕
their disobedience of Meece telling them
他们对Meece的不服从 告诉他们
of them asking me for forgiveness or us
他们要我原谅我们
for forgiveness and then praying
宽恕然后祈祷
together and it ended up with a very
在一起，它结束了一个非常
reassuring hug we really need James 1:5
安慰我们，我们真的需要雅各书1：5
as I was doing this putting together
因为我是做这个放在一起
this outline I thought wow I need to
这个大纲我觉得我需要哇
finish with this verse if anyone lacks
如果有人缺乏，请完成这节经文
wisdom let him ask of God who gives to
智慧让他问上帝给谁
all men liberally and he doesn't chide
所有人都是自由的，他不会嘲笑
as parents we really need that verse now
作为父母，我们现在真的需要这节经文
right before we finish I wanted to give
就在我们结束之前，我想给予
you a loving admonition you've and I'm
你是一个充满爱心的告诫你和我
switching gears on you here before we
在我们之前 切换你的方向
close in prayer you've heard thirty some
在祷告中你已经听过三十个了
of you have been here every weekend and
你每个周末都来过这里
you've heard thirty hours of instruction
你听过三十个小时的教学
that's a lot of stuff we know very well
这是我们非常了解的很多东西
that because just because you've heard
那是因为你听说过
thirty hours of instruction doesn't mean
三十小时的教学并不意味着
you're totally equipped to go disciple
你完全有能力去找门徒
and counsel here's how you get equipped
和律师这里是你如何装备
to disciple and counsel you go start
门徒和劝告你开始吧
disciple and counseling you start using
你开始使用的门徒和辅导
those diagrams we've taught you with
我们教过你的那些图表
people you start practicing using those
你开始练习的人
diagrams on yourself and then that's how
关于你自己的图表然后就是这样的
it really starts to become part of you
它真的开始成为你的一部分
and just starts to become part of your
并开始成为你的一部分
your life and after a while and you just
你的生活，过了一会儿和你一样
start thinking three trees diagram
开始思考三棵树图
you're working with people or a box
你正在和人或盒子一起工作
diagram or whatever it is that you've
图表或什么，那就是你已经
heard in these 30 hours about the heart
在这30个小时里听说过心脏
or all these other biblical principles
或所有这些其他圣经原则
and I just wanted to close with a loving
而我只是想以爱心结束
admonition to remind you that we learned
告诫提醒你我们学到了什么
by doing and I hope that you go try to
通过做，我希望你去尝试
make some disciples with all the
与所有人一起做一些门徒
material that you've heard over the 30
你在30岁时听过的材料
hours I really am in all of you and a
几个小时我真的和你在一起
very very thankful I went home every
非常感谢我每回家
weekend and told my wife how much I
周末告诉我的妻子我有多少
appreciate you and your willingness to
感谢你和你的意愿
come and sit for hours and hours and
进来坐几个小时和
hear biblical principles so we're very
听到圣经的原则，所以我们非常
grateful for how the Lord is going to
感谢主将如何去做
use
使用
you
您